let questions = [
  {
  numb: 1,
  question: " How many brothers does Baviera have? I. Sheeba and mother of Bavitra has 3 children II. Maha the grandmother of Bavitra has only one granddaughter.",
  answer: "If the data in both the statements I and II together are necessary to answer",
  options: [
    "If the data in both the statements I and II together are necessary to answer",
    "If the data either in statement I alone or statement II alone are sufficient to answer",
    "If the data given in both I and II together are not sufficient",
    "If the data in statement II alone are sufficient"
  ]
},
{
numb: 2,
  question: "How many such vowels are there each of which is immediately followed by a symbol? N S E # K 7 Y $ C 8 3 P I T 6 % 9 H U 2 R J * V 5 W A 1 B D G",
  answer: "One",
  options: [
    "Four",
    "Five",
    "One",
    "None of these"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 3,
    question: "How many such consonants are there in the above arrangement, each of which is immediately preceded by either a symbol or number but not immediately followed by a letter? N S E # K 7 Y $ C 8 3 P I T 6 % 9 H U 2 R J * V 5 W A 1 B D G ",
    answer: "Four",
    options: [
      "Four",
    "Five",
    "One",
    "None of these"
    ]
  },
  {
   numb: 4,
      question: "What will come in place of (?) based on the given series? 5A* JV2 UR9 %HT?",
      answer: "I63",
      options: [
      "I63",
      "A5J",
      "PT8",
      "None of these"
    ]
  },
  {
      numb: 5,
         question: "If all the numbers are dropped from the arrangement, which of the following will be the twelfth from the right end of the above arrangement?",
         answer: "%",
         options: [
         "%",
         "I",
         "H",
         "T"
       ]
     },
     {
      numb: 6,
         question: "Newness: Antiquity:: Novelty:?",
         answer: "Oldness",
         options: [
         "Culture",
         "Model",
         "Oldness",
         "Discovery"
       ]
     },
     {
      numb: 7,
         question: "Connoisseur: Art:: Gourmet:?",
         answer: "Food",
         options: [
         "Food",
         "Drink",
         " Flesh",
         "Money"
       ]
     },
     {
      numb: 8,
         question: "Find the next number in the sequence:3, 6, 9, 30, 117……",
         answer: "588",
         options: [
         "192",
         "352",
         "388",
         "588"
       ]
     },
     {
      numb: 9,
         question: "KBJ, LCK, MDL, NEM, _____",
         answer: "OFN",
         options: [
         "OEP",
         "OFN",
         "MEN",
         "PFQ"
       ]
     },
     {
      numb: 10,
         question: "In a class of 20 students, Shreya is 5 from the top and Annie is 7 ranks below Shreya. Find Annie’s rank from the bottom.",
         answer: "9",
         options: [
         "3",
         "5",
         "6",
         "9"
       ]
     },
];